Duncan Payne

1-405-308-9609 Duncan.C.Payne@gmail.com Oklahoma City, OK LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/duncan-payne-3493201ba/

Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/duncan.payne.art/

Design and Software Development Website: https://nouveau-portfolio.vercel.app/

Art Website: https://nouveau-art-portfolio.vercel.app/

I am a creative and hard working artist and designer with experience working in a variety of mediums and software and a passion for visual storytelling.

Skills

Design: Adobe Creative Cloud, Maya, Blender, Procreate

Art: Digital Art, Traditional Art, Writing, Sculpture

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Python3

Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Redux, jQuery Next, React, React Native, Tailwind, MaterialUI

Back-End: Express, Django, Node Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL Other Technologies: Git, NPM, GitHub

Education

Jan 2022 - December 2022 - NuCamp Full Stack Software Development Bootcamp

Aug 2015 - Apr 2020 — University of Science and Arts of Oklahoma, Chickasha, OK Bachelors of Fine Art, Concentration: Expanded Media Graduated Magna Cum Laude

Experience

April 2020 - Present - Multimedia Artist, Self Employed, Oklahoma City, OK

April 2021 - January 2022 – Visitors Experience Associate, Oklahoma Contemporary Arts Center, Oklahoma City, OK

September 2020 - December 2020 - Internship, Artspace Untitled, Oklahoma City, OK

September 2019 - January 2020 – Sales Associate, Bombay Liquor, Chickasha, OK

June 2019 - August 2019 - Volunteer and Contributing Artist, Factory Obscura, Oklahoma City, OK

May 2015 - August 2019 - Electronics Team Member - Summers, Target, Oklahoma City, OK

January 2015 - March 2015 - Sales Associate, Craig's Emporium, Oklahoma City, OK

December 2014 - Sales Associate - Seasonal, GameStop, Oklahoma City, OK